

BALESKOV ALEXANDR

PYTHON JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

Phone

+375 25 7007 412

Email

alexandr_baleskov@mail.ru

linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandr-baleskov/

SKILLS

- Python:
- json, pickle
- SQL
- VSCode
- GiT
- coaching
- requests
- BeautifulSoup

LANGUAGE

- russian
- English (A2) "I plan to level up in the near future"

ABOUT ME

I have 9 months of programming experience in Python. I took a course at the IT Academy in the direction of web programming. I like programming and I'm happy to make it my main profession. I am ready to learn new things and benefit myself and others

EDUCATION

IT-Academy 2022

Python web-application development
Basics of web-technologies HTML/ CSS

 Minsk State Polytechnic College 2007– 2011

Technician Electrician

EXPERIENCE

- Python web-application development
 May 2022-Sep 2022
 - python programming
 - django and flask frameworks
 - sql queries and database types
 - git version control
 - MongoDB
 - REST.API
 - Basics of web-technologies Feb 2022-Mar 2022
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - Bootstrap